<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	
	>
<channel>
	<title>
	Comments on: Ignite TAO Features 11 Rapid Fire Tech Talks + Cocktails 8/17	</title>
	<atom:link href="/articles/ignite-tao-features-11-rapid-fire-tech-talks-cocktails-817/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/articles/ignite-tao-features-11-rapid-fire-tech-talks-cocktails-817/</link>
	<description>Central Oregon&#039;s Startup Community</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 19:48:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.5.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>
		By: Mike Kentley		</title>
		<link>/articles/ignite-tao-features-11-rapid-fire-tech-talks-cocktails-817/#comment-2267</link>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mike Kentley]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 19:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=34867#comment-2267</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I would not have signed up for this Ignite thing if left to my own devices.  To say I am in introvert would be an understatement.  Fortunately, I was not  left to my own devices -- Diane Allen pushed me.    She encourages all of her students to get out there and do things -- so here I am.   I also have lots of things to talk about -- I could come up with 10 good Ignite talks on a moments notice at this point because -- my wife Kathy Hoyt teaches creativity workshops(Fuse Creativity Consulting) and I&#039;m immersed in it (to the point where people tell me things like &quot;Mike, I just don&#039;t understand how your mind works&quot;). When I took Diane&#039;s Public Speaking for Leaders class -- she had us do exercises where we mined our past for good stories and experiences that could be pulled together as-needed for talks, and it turns out I can connect lots of interesting things into a story.  She also had us practice doing off the cuff talks and a supportive environment.  It was awesome!  So -- I would encourage anyone -- male or female -- to start now and work on creativity and public speaking.   It won&#039;t hurt, it will probably be a lot of fun, and you may find that when the next TEDx or Ignite event comes around, you&#039;re rarin&#039; to go with something.   You may find it to be a life changing experience.]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I would not have signed up for this Ignite thing if left to my own devices.  To say I am in introvert would be an understatement.  Fortunately, I was not  left to my own devices &#8212; Diane Allen pushed me.    She encourages all of her students to get out there and do things &#8212; so here I am.   I also have lots of things to talk about &#8212; I could come up with 10 good Ignite talks on a moments notice at this point because &#8212; my wife Kathy Hoyt teaches creativity workshops(Fuse Creativity Consulting) and I&#8217;m immersed in it (to the point where people tell me things like &#8220;Mike, I just don&#8217;t understand how your mind works&#8221;). When I took Diane&#8217;s Public Speaking for Leaders class &#8212; she had us do exercises where we mined our past for good stories and experiences that could be pulled together as-needed for talks, and it turns out I can connect lots of interesting things into a story.  She also had us practice doing off the cuff talks and a supportive environment.  It was awesome!  So &#8212; I would encourage anyone &#8212; male or female &#8212; to start now and work on creativity and public speaking.   It won&#8217;t hurt, it will probably be a lot of fun, and you may find that when the next TEDx or Ignite event comes around, you&#8217;re rarin&#8217; to go with something.   You may find it to be a life changing experience.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
